Kaname and
Kazuto Mokudai.
Are you meeting him for a road date today?
I'm going on a date with him.
I'm going on a road date.
Can we go around?
Here we go.
Are you meeting Mr. Kaname?
Music.
Today...
There's a lot of people here.
Do you have any questions? Something like that.
Oh.
Yeah, so I was wondering if...
I was wondering if we could talk about it together.
Sounds good.
Yes, that sounds good.
And it's a drive, so it's a little bit...
We're going for a drive, so we're going to take it easy.
Let's take it easy.
Sounds good
All right, all right, all right.
Let's go!
You're early!
Kanamekan.
Where are you taking me?
Today.
I'm taking you to a place with a beautiful night view.
Oh, nice.
By the way...
Where?
Somewhere in Roppongi.
I see.
The lights are so beautiful.
Where?
It looks good.
I'm thinking of doing this.
You're a good driver.
How long have you been driving? How long have you had your license?
It's been less than a year.
I've got my learner's permit.
You do.
I've walked here before, but I've never driven.
This is it.
This place is like Shinjuku.
Yes, Shinjuku.
So many people.
Wow, there really are a lot of people!
I'm going to reveal that we were passing through here today.
No, we have to go.
Can I ask you a few questions?
All right.
At first...
What was your first impression of each other?
First impressions?
Come here.
First meeting.
You know, it's not often that two people talk about this.
No, I thought you were a serious girl... at first.
I'm glad.
No, you mean the whole time?
No.
It's really like this, but now with Kazu...
What do you mean, like this?
When you first came to say hello...
Nice to meet you. I'm Ki Dai Akiyuki.
Like, "I'm new here. Nice to meet you.
It was a proper greeting.
But a month later...
But a month later, it's like, "Hey, I'm here!
Please don't do that.
I mean, my impression, my first impression was...
Well, it wasn't so much that he was serious.
I was like, "Oh, here's a really cool guy.
I'm glad.
Yeah, I'm not...
Kaname...
When I joined Ebita as a research student...
It was a time of warring factions.
That's right. It was right around that time.
Everyone was so bright.
Really.
I joined on the way. It wasn't like joining on the way.
I mean, we weren't even there yet.
It was like someone just came in. It was like someone just came in all of a sudden.
I was just trying to learn as I went along.
And KARAME was the only one who seemed calm.
I mean, it's the only one that seems calm.
He doesn't say too much.
But it's not like it's transparent.
What do you mean? I thought there was someone who had a calmness about him.
That's why I couldn't get close to him at first.
But gradually we got to know each other. Akanabe is so sweet.
And we took the same train home.
So we started talking a little bit.
And then we realized we were friends.
It's been five or six years since we met.
We haven't had any arguments. With Kazuto?
Not at all. Not at all.
When we're rushing around, even when we're in a hurry... when Karame and I are going home together...
I mean, no matter what happens, no matter when.
I think we share the same sensibility and the same original way of thinking.
That's why I know what you're thinking even if you don't say much.
There are times when I tend to get sick, and when I get sick...
But Karame is very kind to me. She said we were going home together, so she followed me to my house.
She said she'd follow me home.
That was really touching.
I really thought she was going to collapse.
I see. I remember that.
Next, I'd like to ask you a simple question.
Anything.
What do you respect about each other?
Yeah.
Well, I'll start with what I've been saying all along.
Kazuto is the person closest to me that I admire.
For me...
Yes, yes, yes.
He has everything I don't have.
I see.
Yes, I see.
Like what?
You're not shy, right?
No, I'm not.
I envy you that much.
And also...
I'm going to continue talking about shyness.
You can talk with people you don't know very well, can't you?
I can't wait to talk to them.
That's true.
That's why, with Kazu.
When I'm with someone I don't know, I feel comfortable with just Kazu.
I see.
Also, you have a good sense of humor.
I'm not bad at flirting.
Yeah, you're not bad at flirting at all.
It's more like your planning ability.
You have planning ability.
I don't know...
You have planning skills.
If I say, "Let's go to the sauna," he'll decide where we'll have dinner and then go to the sauna.
He decides everything.
And then I'm asked to look at a map, and I look at the map.
I don't do any crafting.
You know what I admire about you, Salami?
What do you admire about her?
Yes, sir.
Whatever, whatever the situation is.
I can look at it objectively, and I have an opinion that is not interrupted by that market.
Yeah.
So, this may seem simple, but it's surprisingly difficult.
KANAME can be very objective.
You can be objective, and you respect others.
I think it's not so much a letter to yourself as it is a letter to the other person.
It's not like a letter from me.
That's why, when we talk.
It's like we're only talking about what's in our hearts.
Oh.
That's what you're talking about.
Yeah.
Well...
KANAME is certainly not at all
To the people around me...
What?
I've been told I can be shy.
But he's also dynamic.
And he has some interesting ideas.
I respect you as a person.
I, on the other hand, act on the spur of the moment.
I can't hold back what I want to do.
So the point is, you have a good reason not to do something.
You even have a good reason not to do it.
Yes.
That's why I think it's so wonderful.
That's why things can only go well together.
Yes, that's true.
I come up with a lot of ideas.
I come up with a bunch of ideas, and then the canary in the fire says, "Well, that's not right.
Wow, it's true.
They're beautiful.
Nice shoes.
Yes, they are.
Perfect.
What artists have you been into lately?
Lately.
The artist I've been into lately is...
Marlesquin
Oh my gosh!
I'm really into him.
Yeah? What do you think?
I don't know.
I like people who don't take no prisoners.
I see.
Free.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I like your music, too.
It's cool that they're rocking in this day and age.
It's cool that we're rocking in this era.
I see.
I'm really into This is Last.
What can I say about your voice?
Thank you.
Do you listen to music?
I do listen to music.
When do you listen to them? When you are walking?
I like to walk for no reason.
Walking?
Yes.
So, now, when you are alone, what do you do? Is it a hobby? When I'm alone.
When I'm alone, I watch Candlestick or go for a walk.
Sometimes I go for a drive at night. I do that.
Alone? Yeah. Oh, I see.
So, you drive, yes.
I have many memories of driving in my life.
You've been on a lot of road trips at various times, haven't you?
Yes, I have.
Do you have any memories from those times?
I don't have any memories of driving...
But I have a lot of memories of the road trip I took with Jun.
What about it?
We had a lot of fun.
We went to an amusement park in Yokohama.
I heard that.
And we rode all the screams and yelled at the top of our lungs.
On the way home, we talked about our favorite artists.
Jun and I share a lot of the same favorite artists.
I see.
We would play songs and sing along on the way home.
That was fun.
It was a normal date.
And you seem to be having a lot of fun.
Yeah, with JUNK in the passenger seat.
And so is Kazuto.
He keeps talking to me.
Yeah.
I appreciate that when I'm driving.
JUNK talks a lot, too.
JUNK talks a lot.
He talks and sings.
That's a memory.
And then...
I went for a night drive with the craftsmen.
And I thought, "Why am I driving you home when I'm supposed to be doing crafts?
I was driving you home, and you were already...
You were fast asleep.
You're lying.
I said, "Here we are," and the first thing you said was, "Home.
That's the worst.
What cities do you go to these days?
Yokohama for the beach.
And I like Enoshima.
Enoshima.
Don't go to Enoshima either.
I got a present for my boyfriend.
I've got one for my boyfriend.
So...
I think I'll just let him talk in the passenger seat.
Have some waffles.
Woooo!
You don't mind?
Thank you!
Oh, I'm so happy.
But if you asked me to open it...
I threw away the waffle.
I'm so happy!
I love waffles!
There's a face on the bag that I've seen so many times!
Yum!
Thank you so much!
No, no, no, no. I'm glad.
Okay, I'll just have a waffle.
I know you're probably thirsty.
Drink some water if you need to.
Yes, sir.
That's good.
Kakka drive.
Yeah. - Okay.
Do you have any personal goals?
Personal goals?
Yeah. - Yeah.
You mean she's not famous?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you're in a group, you can talk to her when you're in a long house.
No, I haven't been in a play for a long time.
Acting?
I'm in a play all the time.
I see.
You don't have to be tied to a role.
I want to play the role I've been given, and I want to be someone who can play that role.
I also have a strong desire to go abroad.
It's my dream to work abroad.
I want to work abroad, too.
You've always wanted to go abroad, haven't you?
Yes, I do.
Overseas?
That's great.
No, I don't.
What do you think you'll be doing in the future? Me, my partner.
I think I'm gonna start my own brand.
Clothing?
Clothing.
And of course, you'll be working at your day job.
I can see you doing something else in the future.
Yeah, I'd like to do something.
Here it comes.
There it is. - Here it is.
Roppongi.
It's here. - It's here.
It's here. It's here.
Oh, oh, oh.
It's here.
Beautiful.
Wow, so sparkly!
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
Look, it's so beautiful!
So beautiful!
Oh, my God.
This is beautiful.
It's so beautiful!
I'm glad I came again this year.
This is beautiful!
Kanawoo happy? I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
You should definitely use that.
It's so good.
This is great.
I love winter the best.
I like to watch the lights and stuff all the time.
It's great.
And I'm glad I came with Kaname.
But you know what I realized today?
We talk all the time.
Maybe more.
I could probably talk a lot of nonsense.
It'll be fun to get a better view of the city.
I know, I know.
I like the idea of a road trip.
First one? This one.
Isn't this the first one? The driving project.
And it's the first time we've talked about it, so... Yeah, and you've never seen me drive before.
It's like... it's summer and we're at the beach. No, it's nice.
I'd love to go to the beach.
Even if it's not the two of us.
Of course, you'll be able to drive a big car.
That's great.
Okay, well, I'll just...
I'd like to enjoy some space just the two of us.
Okay.
See you later, guys.